We are fighting now only exclusively
у нас воюет сейчас только исключительно
contract service is not this is
контрактная служба не это это
nonsense
брехня
Hello Good evening I
Здравствуйте Добрый вечер Я у Россиян
am asking the Russians how you see the end of yours
спрашиваю как вы видите окончание сво
for
для
you For me yes As a
вас Для меня да Как
citizen it will not change in any way I will
гражданин никак не поменяется Я буду
live the same way as I do not not how you would like yours to
жить так же как я нене как Вы хотели бы
end
чтобы закончилась
Well  firstly, so that Ukraine does not
сво Ну во-первых чтобы Украина не
join NATO this time and secondly,
вступила в НАТО это раз а во-вторых
so that Donetsk, Lugansk and Crimea remain
чтобы Донецк Луганск и Крым остался
within the Russian Federation
всё-таки В составе Российской Федерации
and
а
Kherson. Well, that is, if, roughly speaking,
Херсон Ну то есть если вот грубо говоря
on the borders that we exist
на тех границах которые мы существуем
today, yes, that is, it turns out A  you
сегодня м да то есть получается А вы же
accepted in the Constitution a little
в Конституции приняли немножко
differently that Kherson and the entire
по-другому что и Херсон и вся область
Kherson region I I don’t know such subtleties
Херсонской я Я тонкостей таких не знаю
you asked me, I understand
вы у меня поинтересовались понял да
that if the war ends tomorrow it
то если война закончится завтра то она
will end on the borders on which
закончится на тех границах на которые
our state is located, but plus so that
находятся наши государство но плюс чтобы
Ukraine does not join  in NATO that's all like
Украина не вступила в НАТО вот и всё как
me Well the question Yes the question Why should Ukraine
я Ну вопрос Да вопрос А зачем Украине
stop
останавливаться
then well stop in the sense of where to
тогда ну останавливаться в смысле где
stop you look you say it turns out
останавливаться вот смотрите вы говорите
Ukraine must agree
получается Украина должна согласиться
that this will now be the territory of Russia yes yes and
что это будет теперь территория России
transfer the territory yes yes look
а передать территорию да да вот смотрите
what needs to happen for Ukraine  took it
что должно случиться чтобы Украина взяла
and handed it over. That’s how it is, how you see it, this is a
и передала Вот как это как вы видить это
complete capitulation of Ukraine, yes, yes, this is
это капитуляция Украины полно да да вот
what Russia needs to do for Ukraine to
что нужно сделать России чтобы Украина
capitulate, but Ukraine hasn’t capitulated for 2 years,
капитулировала вот Украина 2 года уже не
well, firstly, there is zero
капитулировала ну во-первых это ноль
support from the West, zero support from the United States, and
поддержки Запада ноль поддержки США и
after you there will be no support
после того как вам поддержка не будет
provided thulite literally through me That is, it
оказана тулит буквально через ме То есть
turns out yes And if we
получается да А если нам будут
continue to be there for 5-10 years, then
продолжать до сих пор там 5-10 лет то вы
in short you will suffer, suffer and
короче будете мучаться мучиться и
suffer Yes, well, if they continue to
мучаться Да ну если Вам будут продолжать
allocate funds to you, then first of all
выделять денежные средства то в первую
men will die, and
очередь погибнут мужчины во вторую
secondarily women will die  unfortunately
очередь погибнут женщины к сожалению
the women got it So it’s so interesting Wait, it turns out
женщи понял Так так интересно то
you, uh, somehow you’re not fighting with men
ээ вы как-то воюете не мужчинами
Well, we’re fighting a contract soldier We do
Да ну мы воюем контрактника У нас есть
n’t have you fighting with men and Contra mobiles There’s a
не вы воюете мужчинами и Контра мобили
bunch of mobiles You’ve got a lot of them, like, no,
Зро куча мобили Зро их у вас типа да не
what’s your name
нуте Вас как зовут
Andromeda  like
Андромед как
Androniki it’s like Andronikos the Greek No not
андроники это как Андроник грек Нет не
Andrei Aro good Greek Greek look
Андрей Аро хорошо грек грек вот смотрите
we are fighting now only exclusively
у нас воюет сейчас только исключительно
contract
контрактная
service this is nonsense nonsense no you have
служба это это брехня брехня нет у вас
a lot of mobile phones
куча мобили
called not What do you think you look
званных не Как вы считаете вы смотри
good If you only have contract soldiers
хорошо Если у вас только контрактники А
What’s the point  mobilization, you
в чём же суть мобилизации у вас
had mobilization a year ago in September,
мобилизация была год назад в сентябре
so where did these people go? They
так А куда делись Эти люди Они что
died, they don’t serve, 300,000 people are
умерли они не служат 300.000 человек
mobile. Let’s
мобили Зро о
either build a dialogue, or
с давайте мы или диалог выстраиваем или
let’s build a dialogue and clarify during the dialogue.
го мы диалог и в процессе диалога
I want to understand the mobiles. They’re
уточняем Я хочу понять мобили Зро они ж
not contract soldiers.  true Of course not And
не контрактники правда Конечно нет А
when we had mobile phones Zro you
когда у нас были мобили Зро вы вы
said that you only have
сказали что у вас только
contract soldiers now yes And where did the
контрактники сейчас да А куда делись
mobile phones go No no I’m telling you that
мобилие Нет нет я вам говорю про то что
until September they recruited 300,000 mobile phones
до в сентябре набирали 300.000 мобили
Zro this is them This is the second year They are
Зро это они Воть второго года Они
fighting Why are they you front  they
воюют Почему они вы фронт
saw the front stretched over more than
видели фронт растянулся более чем на
1000 km They are fighting, they are fighting only
1000 км Они воюют воюют только
contract soldiers, also called into mobiles,
контрактники тоже во мобили званные
of course, and they are fighting, they are fighting, but before that you
конечно же и воюют воюют да то вы перед
said that only contract soldiers are fighting in your country
этим сказали что у вас воюют только
And now
контрактники А теперь
Goris is fighting only contract service and
Горис воюют только контрактная служба и
recruiting Wait, how is
набирают Подождите как сейчас воюет
only contract service fighting now? Well  now the Zro mobiles are
только контрактная Ну сейчас мобили Зро
now fighting, let me say, you are silent,
сейчас воюют давайте я говорю вы молчите
you don’t let me with I’m just saying
вы не Давайте с Я просто вы говорите
some unrelated nonsense, let you
какой-то несвязанный бред давайте вы
speak, I’m telling you this, you
говори я я вам вот что говорю вы
say that you have a contract
говорите что у вас сеча контрактная
service, but at the same time you say that they
служба но при этом же вы говорите что у
recruited from you  Zro mobiles and they are also
вас набрали мобили Зро и они тоже сейчас
fighting now That is, now the mobiles are fighting or
воюют То есть сейчас мобилие воюют или
wait, I say you are silent, you
подождите я говорю вы молчите вы же сами
said it yourself, this formula turns out And when
сказали этот формулу получается И когда
you have both contract soldiers and Zro mobiles fighting at the same time,
у вас воюют одновременно и контрактники
right or
и мобили Зро правильно или
wrong You are done, let me
неправильно Вы закончили разрешаю вам
tell you, are the Greeks really
сказать вы греки реально
like that or just
такие или только
you are Greece with an ancient history because
ты Греция с древней историей потому что
we are all so great
мы все такие великие Да отвечайте на
Yes, answer the question Let’s Well, I’m telling you again,
вопрос Давайте Ну я вам говорю ещё раз
we had partial mobilization in
мобилизация частичная у нас была в 2022
2022, in the month of September, we recruited
году в сентябре месяце ко нас набрали
300,000 people. So where did they go? NT
300.000 человек Так куда они делись НТ
stretched out and we needed to recruit
растянулся и нам необходимо было набрать
that
то
number where they are now, military
количество где они сейчас военной
specialization g they are now damn Greek, well
специализации г они сейчас блин грек ну
shut up, where are they now, these 300,000 Are they
помолчи да где они сейчас эти 300000 Они
fighting or
воюют или
not Well, okay, these 300,000 What are they doing
нет Ну хорошо эти 300.000 Что делают
now not a Greek wait No no no Russian
сейчас не грек подожди Не не нет русский
Look no I’m like an imperious Greek I’m
Смотри не я как властный грек тебе ещё
telling you again you tell me if  they were recruited They are
раз говорю ты скажи если их набрали Они
fighting Either yes or no just tell them
воюют Или да или нет просто скажи воюют
those contract soldiers are fighting now or oh Tey dialogue
сейчас те контрактники или ой Тей диалог
then I ask you again
потом я тебя ещё раз спрашиваю вот
just answer the mobiles
просто ответь мобили
ask me and Ask you
поинтересоваться у меня а Спрашивай ты
from yours or not What happened to the
будешь у сво или нет Что случилось с
mobiles Zro they are either fighting Or they are already
мобили Зро они либо воюют Либо они уже
died, it turns out, come on, decide, let me
сдохли получается давай реши разрешай
answer, you’re done, I give you permission
ответить ты закончил Я тебе разрешаю
to answer, come on, yes,
ответить давай да да ты свои вот эти
keep these little vibes to yourself, I’ll
мелкие флюиды оставь при себе я тебе
tell you, initially in 2022 there was
скажу изначально в 2022 году была
actually a mobilization. Yes, and in the
действительно мобилизация Да и в
Russian Federation, 300,000 people were called up for service
Российской Федерации призвали на службу
in the second year.  it was the
человек которые в ть втором году Это был
month of
сентябрь месяц
September, they were sent to the front, but
сентябрь они были направлены на фронт но
again, after a certain
опять же они после определённой
training and with a certain
подготовки и с определённой
specialization of military specialization, they were
специализации военной специализации были
sent there
отправлены туда
and damn now new ones have arrived. Well, I’m asking, I
и бля сейчас новые пришли Ну я спрашиваю
understand, I
Всё я понял
earned money, look, they are fighting now,
зарабатывал смотри то Они воюют сейчас
those who have gained 300,000. Are they fighting or
те которых набрали 300.000 Они воюют или
not?  Yes or no dude you answer my
нет Да или нет чува ты мне ответь на
question you answer the question first no
вопрос тым ответь сначала на вопрос нет
Tell me these 300,000 Are they fighting or
Скажи у вас эти 300.000 Они воюют или
not just say no you are
нет просто скажи не ты пять раз
repeating the same thing five times they were recruited
повторяешь одно и тоже их набрали
they were trained at the front Are they fighting or not Yes
обучили они на фронте Они воюют или нет
or
Да или
no are
нет
you finished
ты закончил
No  let's
Нет давай
continue with your head like that,
продолжай головой вот так
nod and
кивни
look very
н смотри очень
simply like for a hamster Say yes or
просто бе Как для хомячка Скажи да или
no Yes or
нет Да или
no Or
нет
let's let you
Или давай разрешай
talk Well, I honestly and frankly say
поговорить Ну я честно откровенно говорю
you're Greek Where do you live now If it's not a
ты грек Ты где живёшь сейчас Если не
secret, of course in
секрет конечно в
Thessaloniki Thessaloniki is, well, what kind of country
Салониках Салоники - это ну страна какая
is Greece?  unexpectedly right And why do
это Греция неожиданно пра А почему у
you have a flag of Ukraine because I support
тебя флаг Украина потому что поддерживаю
Ukraine And why do you support it is
Украину А в чём ты её поддерживаешь в
that I find all sorts of morons using
том что нахожу всяких дебилов сеча
roulette and ask Like, is their
рулетке и спрашиваю Типа так воюют ихние
mobile fighting or not fighting, of course the
мобилие или не воюют конечно воюют
Morova are fighting, all that mobile is fighting, you
морова всё то мобилие воюют ты
confirmed finally they are not fighting  only
подтвердил наконец-то воют не только
contract soldiers A and mobile, well, those who are
контрактники А и мобилие ну тех которые
300,000 oh, that is, look, you
300.000 о то есть смотри ты
finally 10 minutes he gave birth to this idea,
наконец-то 10 минут он родил эту мысль
gave birth to the idea that mobiles ZRO are also fighting
родил мысль что мобили Зро ие тоже воюют
hallelujah
аллилуйя
public please, this is just awesome,
публику пожалуйста это просто офигенно
finally, that is, you admitted that it’s
наконец то есть ты признал что у вас
not only
воюет не только
Contra that is fighting with you  300,000 in the VM year who were
Контра 300.000 в ВМ году которые были
mobile again, that is, not only let’s
мобили ещё раз то есть не только давай
not only
так воюют не только
contract soldiers fight like this, I’ll repeat it to you again If
контрактники я тебе ещё раз повторю Если
you don’t
ты не Оду
eat VM
ешь ВМ
year, wait, let’s do this Listen to the question
году подожди давай так Послушай вопрос
carefully, strain Listen to the question You
внимательно напряги Послушай вопрос Ты
said that only contract soldiers are fighting in your country,
сказал что у вас воюют только
first point  the second thesis
контрактники первый тезис второй тезис
you said that yes, the called mobiles also
ты сказал что да мобили званные тоже
fight, then they receive
воюют то получа
T then the contract soldiers you deceived that time yes
Т то контрактники ты обманул тот раз да
Or you were mistaken Yes, you are
Или ошибся
finished, let me
Да ты закончил разрешай тебе
tell you, to be honest, you
сказать ты честно говоря ты много на
take a lot on yourself Well, I allow myself to take a lot on How to
Ну позволяю себе брать много на Как
say your days are big Well, a little
сказать у вас дни большой Ну немножко
you will be crushed later this is all the
вас придавит потом это со
time people with such a lack of intelligence
вс люди с таким отсутствием интеллекта
Damn, they live shorter than damn up to 30
Блин доживают короче блин до 30
years old, this is some
лет это блин
kind of damn magic, subscribe to my Telegram
какая-то магия подпишись на мий Telegram
right away, Ovin and
прям зараз овин а
popk, so much more and more
попк це дуже и дуже
respectfully
важливо